VOLODYMYR SEMKIV

Eindhoven, The Netherlands semkivvolodya@gmail.com +380977901872

Front-end Developer

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Bash, SQL, MongoDB, GraphQL, Material-UI, HTML5, CSS, Less, Gulp, Git, Figma, Photoshop. Fortran, Matlab, Wolfram Mathematica, Comsol.

PROJECTS:

• Portfolio https://sem19.github.io/Portfolio/

• Fitness https://sem19.github.io/fitnes/

Funiro Website for the sale of furniture (JavaScript, React)

Shelter for pets
A small application to help animals via finding houses for

them

SoCoders https://dev.socoders.com/

We are building a project for the IT engineering community. That is, we strive to become an organization-club of engineers, for mutual assistance in maintaining skills in a market-relevant state and improving qualifications, cooperation on mutual projects, exchange of experience, assistance in the implementation of ideas and projects. We are building our app to serve all of this. A lot of functionality is still not implemented, that is, we are in the very early stages.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

SoCoders 08/2021 – present

Front-End Engineer

INTERNSHIP:

University of Groningen 09/2019 – 10.2019

Thesis: "Vibration of circular membranes with heavy disks inside"

Ye. O. Paton Electric Welding Institute 01/2019 – 02.2019

Thesis: "Electronic broadcasting and spectroscopy methods in

diagnostics of metallic constructions "

EDUCATION:

Main Academy 02/2021 – 06/2021

Course "Front-End Development"

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv, Ukraine

M.Sc., Theoretical and Applied Mechanics

Thesis: "Reflection of Coriolis dispersed plane waves on an elastic half-media"

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv, Ukraine

B.Sc., Theoretical and Applied Mechanics

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv, Ukraine Thesis: "Perturbation Method in calculation of deformed state of varying thicknesses plates"

LANGUAGES:

English, Ukrainian, Russian

09/2017 - 07/2019

09/2013 - 07/2017